Activities and Organizations Records UA024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs, 1894 -- 1982; 1912 -- 1982; UA024.002; 1.7 Linear Feet; 18 Digital Object(s)
  - Tufts Mandolin Club, 1916 -- 1917; UA024.002.023.00027 (Box Shared 4)
  - Semi-centennial rehearsal group, Tufts College, 1936-05-16; UA024.002.023.00028 (Box Shared 4)
    This photograph was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversized materials.
  - Tufts College choir, 1902 -- 1903; UA024.002.023.00029 (Box Shared 4)
    This photo was found uncatalogued in the stacks in the summer of 2008. Note its different location; it is housed in a box with other oversized materials.
  - Spring sing, 1962; UA024.002.DO.00662; Unknown (Box Shared 93)
    Students; Student activities; Singing; Singers; Women; Choir
  - Yearbook picture of Delta Tau Delta, 1961; UA024.002.DO.01493; Unknown (Box Shared 61)
    Student activities; Portraits, Group; Students; Greek letter societies; photographic print; Delta Tau Delta